{
    "id": "aaa00dacae8642afad069da24e836e3c",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I understand that he …………………… .. absent yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Wood always …………………… .. on water.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "float",
                "floats",
                "will float"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………… heavily for a week and the rivers are overflowing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rained",
                "is raining",
                "has been raining"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "There are some birds that …………………… . every year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "migrate",
                "migrates",
                "migrating"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. to Singapore once.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have gone",
                "have been",
                "had gone",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… .. dinner an hour ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………… .. nothing to eat since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "have had"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Her health has improved since she ……………………… to her native village.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "has returned",
                "had returned"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will catch the first bus that …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "come",
                "is coming",
                "comes"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "See that the patient …………………… . complete rest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "gets",
                "got"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}